반양성자에 스핀을
반대로 바꾸고
And reverse the spin
on the antiproton...
감마가 알파로 변하고
and gamma becomes alpha...
(-i,0) 매트릭스로 곱하면
Multiplied by a matrix
of negative I comma zero...
결정적 증거를 얻었군
And there we have it.
9시 이후에는
돌대가리가 된다는 걸
Conclusive proof that I am
absolutely worthless
after 9:00.
CREEPY VOICE:
Sheldon...
Hmm.
(electrical crackling, popping)
알겠다
All right, all right.
무슨 수작인지 뻔하네
I see what's going on.
할로윈 전이라
장난 치는 거지?
A little pre-Halloween
hijinkery.
(moaning, chains rattling,
cackling)
귀신 울음소리
A ghostly moan,
찰랑거리는 쇠사슬
a rattling of chains,
낄낄대는 마녀
a witch's cackle.
흉가의 3대 구성 요소지
The trifecta
of haunted house cliches.
비명 대신에 하품이 나오네
Instead of "Eek,"
I say, "Yawn."
CREEPY VOICE:
Sheldon...
벽에는 피가 흐르지만
Oh, the walls
are dripping blood,
페놀프탈렌 지시약을
which looks nothing like
a phenolphthalein indicator
탄산나트륨 용액에
넣은 거잖아
exposed to a sodium carbonate
solution.
'지옥에서 보자 쉘든'
"See you in hell Sheldon."
여기서 제일 무서운 건
쉼표가 빠졌다는 거야
The most frightening thing about
that is the missing comma.
Ah.
Okay, all right.
이건 조금 괜찮았어
That one was clever.
빨랫줄을 타고 내려오는
야광 해골
Skeleton with phosphorous
on a zip line.
이제 나와라, 장난꾸러기들
Come on out,
merry pranksters.
얼굴 좀 보자
Take a bow.
(laughing)
네 표정이 예술이었어
You should've seen your face.
살짝 놀라서
동공이 커진 것 뿐이야
Yes, there's
nothing quite like
the slightly widened eyes
of mildly startled.
무서웠다고 인정 좀 하지
Come on, admit it.
We got you, Sheldon.
무서우려면
깜짝 놀라야 하는데
Please, fright depends
on an element of surprise.
모두 알다시피
The simple fact is,
내가 훨씬 똑똑하니까
because I am much smarter
than you,
너네가 어떻게 나올지
예상할 수 있어
and able to anticipate your
actions, it is highly unlikely
그러니 내가 놀랄
일은 절대 없지
that you two rubes
could ever surprise me.
맞아
He's probably right.
너무 똑똑해서 안 먹히네
We can't beat him.
He's just too smart.
Gentlemen.
(screams)
(laughing)
기절하는 데에 돈 건 사람?
Who had money
on "faints"?
난 오줌 쌀 거라고 했어
I had "pee his pants."
어디 보자
Hang on.
모두의 예상이 맞았네
Looks like everyone's a winner.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
DC 기타 미국드라마 갤러리
The Big Bang Theory 5x07
The Good Guy Fluctuation
Original Air Date on October 27, 2011
자막 공대언니
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
조심해, 쉘든
Oh. Watch out, Sheldon.
캐스퍼라는 꼬마 유령이야
This little boy Casper
is a g-g-g-ghost!
웃기시네
Droll.
오줌 지린 성인 남자가
Not as droll as a grown man
기절한 것보다는 재미없지
passed out in a puddle
of his own urine.
꽤 재밌네
That was pretty droll.
암모니아 냄새도 나고
With a hint of ammonia.
맘껏 놀려라
Yes, enjoy your japes,
gentlemen.
겁쟁이 연구자한테
한 방 먹인 줄 알겠지만
You think you've poked fun
at a milquetoast academic.
이건 기억해둬
Well, you've forgotten
one thing:
나는 외로운 별의 아들이야
I am also a son
of the Lone Star state.
뼈속까지 텍사스라고
I'm Texas through and through.
우리는 당하고는 못 살아
And we know how to settle
scores down there.
못 믿겠으면 멕시코에 물어봐
If you doubt me, ask Mexico.
9시방향에 떴다
(quietly):
Hot girl, nine o'clock.
동시에 쳐다보지 마
Don't everybody look at once!
만화방에 웬 여자야?
What is she doing
in a comic book store?
길을 잃었나봐
I don't know, she might be lost.
한 수 가르쳐줄게
Doesn't matter. Watch and learn.
안녕
- Hi.
Um... it-it-it...
닥쳐
Shut up.
넥스트맨 사려고?
Are you getting
this Next Men?
응, 21권이잖아
Uh, yeah. It's
issue number 21.
헬보이가 처음으로 등장해
First appearance of Hellboy.
몇 년 동안 찾아다녔는데
I know. I've been
looking for it for years.
미안
Sorry.
너한테 관심 있는 척 하고
Hey, if I pretended
to hit on you,
네가 집중 못할 때
뺏어갈 수 있지 않을까?
could I distract you
enough to sneak it away?
그럼 초능력을 악용하는 거잖아
Yes, but you'd be using
your superpowers for evil.
크립토니언 아빠가
그렇게 가르치지는 않았지
Damn, I'm forbidden by my
Kryptonian father to do so.
난 앨리스야
I'm Alice.
레너드라고 해
Leonard.
귀엽다, 레너드
You're very cute, Leonard.
고마워,
그냥 너 가져
Thanks. You, too. You know,
go ahead and take it.
그런 나쁜 짓은 안 할래
No, no. No, no,
I-I did evil.
교환은 어때?
Would you be open
to a trade?
그러지 뭐
Uh, yeah, yeah,
sure, I guess.
Okay. Here.
내 번호야
This is my number.
연락해
Call me.
손에 땀 차서 미안
Sorry, palm's a little sweaty.
저건 뭐라고 쓴 거야?
What's that word?
앨리스
- Alice.
- Oh, right, your name.
'페니스'가 아니였구나
That makes more
sense than "penis."
또 보자
Later.
만화방에서 여자 번호 딴 거야?
Did we just see you pick up
a girl in a comic book store?
저기 영웅들이랑
벽에 사진 걸어줄게
'Cause if you did, you get
your picture up there
on the Wall of Heroes.
그런 거 아냐
No, I don't think
I picked her up.
난 여친도 있잖아
Besides, I have a girlfriend.
어쨌든 넌 기록을 세웠어
Doesn't matter. This is the
closest anyone's ever come.
벽에 올려줄게
You're going on
the wall, my friend.
우편함 확인해봐
Be sure to check the mail.
벌써 몇 번째야?
왜 그러는데?
How many times are you gonna
tell me? What's with you?
수상해할 건 없어
Nothing. It's not suspicious
that I'm fixating.
내 성격이 그렇잖아
It's consistent with
my personality.
알았어
Right.
Hey, guys.
또 할로윈 캔디 샀어?
More Halloween candy?
어제도 잔뜩 사오더니
Didn't you just buy
a bunch of it yesterday?
없어졌어
Oh. Yeah.
That's gone.
생리전증후군이랑
할로윈이 겹쳐서 힘들어
It's a rough month when
Halloween and PMS
hit at the same time.
레너드는 잡담할 시간 없어
Leonard doesn't have time
to chat, he has to get the mail.
진정해,
곧 열어볼게
Will you relax?
I'll get it in a minute.
- 일은 어땠어?
- 우편함 열어봐
- How was work?
- Open the mail!
잠시만
Excuse me.
전단지 밖에 없잖아
A couple of circulars,
nothing important.
- 쟤는 왜 저래?
- 기다려
- What's with him?
- Hang on.
(air horn blares,
screams)
넌 텍사스 출신이지만,
난 뉴저지야
You might be from Texas,
but I'm from New Jersey.
(air horn blares)
이것 봐
Check it out.
2년 전 코믹 콘에서
짐리가 그려줬어
Jim Lee drew this
of me two years ago
at Comic Con.
뭘 입은 거야?
What are you wearing?
코믹 콘에는 다 그래
Well, you know,
it's Comic Con.
썬더캣츠의 라이온오야
I'm Lion-O from
ThunderCats.
인기 많았겠네
Wow, you must have
gotten so laid.
제시카 알바가
털을 쓰다듬긴 했어
No. But Jessica Alba
did rub my furry belly.
(laughs)
내가 그린 만화 볼래?
Want to see a comic I draw?
정말?
작가였어?
You're kidding.
You have your own book?
그냥 내 얘기를 그려봤어
Yeah. It's kinda
based on my life.
멋지다
Cool.
Oh, look.
츄바카 상의를 입은
남자랑 섹스하고 있네
That's you having
sex with a guy
in the top half of
a Chewbacca costume.
코믹 콘?
Comic Con?
그럴 것 같지만 아냐
You'd think, but no.
정말 소질 있다
You're very talented.
This is really good.
혹시...
Did you do...
내 만화랑 헬보이 교환해도 될까?
So, can I trade you
my comic for the Hellboy?
내 차를 가져도 돼
You can have my car.
이런
Oh, dear.
Oh, dear...
Oh, dear, oh, dear.
Oh, dear... oh, dear.
Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
퓨렐
Purell, Purell,
Purell, Purell.
좋은 아침이야, 쉘든
Good morning, Sheldon.
그렇지?
It is, isn't it?
(gasps)
Oh, bother.
항상 이런 식이지
Isn't that just
always the way?
스테이플러를 쓰려고 하면
침이 떨어져 있어
You go to staple something,
and you're out of staples.
아까 문방구에 갔을 때
알았으면 좋았을 걸
Gosh, I wish I'd known
that earlier today
when I was at Staples.
저기 클립 쓰면 되잖아
You have a thing of paper clips
right there.
클립보다 단단한 게 필요해
No, no, I need something more
permanent to join these papers.
서랍에 스테이플 두지 않아?
Say, don't you keep staples
in your top desk drawer?
모르겠어
I don't know. Maybe.
확인 좀 해줘
Be a lamb and check.
그래
All right.
(gasps)
아니, 이게 누구야?
Who do we have here?
무서운 뱀이야
It's a snake.
A terrifying snake.
누가 서랍에 가뒀을까?
Oh, did some bad man
put us in a drawer?
그만 얘기해
Stop talking like that.
넌 무서워서 말이 없어야 해
You've been rendered
speechless by fear.
생물과 실험실에 가서
맛난 쥐를 찾아보자
Let's go to the biology lab and
find you some nice yummy mice.
인도인을 뱀으로
놀라게 하려 하다니
I tried to scare an Indian
with a snake.
쿠퍼, 잘 좀 해봐
Come on, Cooper.
You're better than this.
들어와
(knocking)
It's open.
잠깐 시간 있어?
Hey, you got a minute?
물론이지
Yeah, sure, come on in.
고마워
Thanks.
맥앤치즈 먹을래?
Want some mac and cheese?
유당이랑 가스 때문에 안돼
No. Lactose. Gas.
- 와인 한 잔?
- 아황산염, 편두통
- Glass of wine?
- No. Sulfites. Migraines.
할로윈 캔디를 주고 싶은데
Okay, well, I'd offer
you Halloween candy,
이미 다 먹었어
but that's gone.
무슨 일이야?
So, what's up?
전에 사귄 사이잖아
Okay, we used to go out, right?
어쩐지 익숙하다 했어
Oh, my God, that's
where I know you from.
연애 관련 고민이 있는데
I'm dealing with a situation and
it's kind of about my love life,
너랑 얘기하기
좀 이상할 수 있어
so I know that might be weird
for us to talk about,
그런데 다른 친구들은
이 분야에 쓸모 없잖아
but in this area, as you know,
all my other friends
are just so stupid.
뭔데?
All right, what's going on?
얘기해도 돼?
So, you're okay
talking about this?
- 응
- 정말 괜찮아?
- Yes.
- You're sure it's not weird.
괜찮다니까
It's okay.
너도 비슷한 고민이 생기면
You know what, if you ever want
to talk to me about a problem
언제든지 나한테 말해
in your life with a guy,
then I would be fine with that.
전에 내가 사귀던 남자가 있는데
Okay, good, because there's
this one guy I used to date
와인이랑 치즈를
입에 쑤셔 넣고 싶어
who's about to be force-fed
wine and cheese
계속 말만 돌리고 있거든
if he doesn't get to the point.
Okay, uh...
here it is.
여자친구가 있는 남자가
바람 피는 건지 아닌지...
Is it cheating
if a guy has a girlfriend...
맞을 거야
Yeah, probably.
더 들어줘
Come on.
미안, 계속 해봐
I'm sorry, go ahead.
괜찮은 여자를 만났는데
I met this girl,
and she's great.
나랑 공통점이 많아
we have a lot in common.
했어?
Did you guys do it?
아니, 그냥 조금 놀았어
No. We just made out a little.
이런, 나쁜 남자네
Oh, look at you, you bad boy.
프리야 얘기는 했어?
Did you tell her
about Priya?
그러고 싶었는데
입이 혀로 가득 찼었어
Well, I was gonna, but
there were too many
tongues in my mouth.
징그러워
That's gross.
난 그런 남자가 아냐
Here's the thing,
I-I'm not one of those guys
여자친구를 두고
다른 여자랑 잘 수 없어
who sneaks around and sleeps
with more than one woman.
좋은 자세야
Well, good for you.
나도 그런 남자가
되고 싶은 게 문제야
The problem is, I want
to be one of those guys.
그럼 걔랑 자고
프리야한테는 거짓말 해
So sleep with the new girl
and lie to Priya.
나답지 않잖아
Oh, that's not who I am.
그럼 새 여자랑 그만 만나
All right, then break it off
with the new girl.
그건 너무 성급하지
Now, let's not do anything rash.
정말 매력적이야
She's really hot.
걔가 그렇게 좋으면
If you like this girl so much,
프리야랑 끝내면 되잖아?
why don't you just
end things with Priya?
프리야랑은 사랑하는 사이야
Priya and I are in love.
언젠가는 결혼할 생각이고
I think we could
get married someday.
두 여자를 차지하고
모두 만족하길 바라고 있네
Leonard, you're looking for
a way to sleep with both women
and have everybody
be happy about it.
이제야 말이 통하는군
Now we're getting somewhere.
네 직감은 어때?
What does your gut tell you?
페니한테 물어보면
알려줄 거라고 하네
"Go ask Penny;
she'll know what to do."
안녕, 하워드
Hello, Howard.
날 놀라게 만든 건
장난이라는 거 알아
I've realized that you
scaring me was all in jest.
축하해,
성공적이었어
Allow me to say, job well done.
(buzzing, grunting)
(buzzing, grunting continue)
(buzzing stops)
(panting)
완벽해
Perfect.
뭐하는 거야?
What are you doing?
과학이야,
넌 이해 못해
Science. You
wouldn't understand.
그래, 나갔다 올게
Hey, well, see you.
I'm going out.
(exhales)
나가는 거 아니였어?
I thought you were
leaving the apartment.
결정을 못 하겠어
Yeah, me, too.
I can't make up my mind.
개랑 깡패들이 두려워서?
Are you concerned
because the world is filled
with big dogs and bullies?
아니, 윤리적인 문제야
No. I'm having a moral crisis.
도움이 될지 모르겠지만
Well, if it's of
any help, I've read
윤리학자들이 쓴 책은
다 읽어봤어
all the great
moral philosophers,
닥터 수스를 포함해서
including Dr. Seuss.
에라 모르겠다
Oh, what the hell.
만화방에서 만난
앨리스랑 약속이 있는데
I'm supposed
to go see that girl
from the comic book store,
Alice, but I don't know
프리야랑 사귀고 있어서
만나도 되는지 모르겠어
if I should, because
I'm going out with Priya,
프리야는 인도에 있지만
but she's in India.
성적 충실 의무에
대한 문제니까
All right. So the topic at hand
is sexual fidelity.
닥터 수스는 없어도 되겠군
Probably won't be relying
on Seuss here.
'One Fish, Two Fish,
Red Fish, Blue Fish'라는 책은
Although One Fish, Two Fish,
Red Fish, Blue Fish
적용할 수도 있겠다
might be
surprisingly applicable.
계속 해
Go on.
Well...
인생의 끝에서는
they say
at the end of your life,
그때가지 한 일보다
you regret the stuff
you didn't do
하지 못한 일을
더 후회한다잖아
more than the stuff
that you did,
그리고 난 앨리스랑
하고 싶은 게 확실해
and I'm pretty sure Alice
is the stuff I want to do.
독일의 철학자 니체는
도덕을 이렇게 보았지
You know,
the German philosopher,
Friedrich Nietzsche,
believed that morality
지배자들이 민중을 통제하기
위한 하나의 수단이라고
is just a fiction used by the
herd of inferior human beings
to hold back
the few superior men.
도움 되는 말이다
That actually does help.
매독으로 죽었어
It's worth noting that
he died of syphilis.
젠장
Screw it,
그냥 갈래
I'm going.
On your way home,
돌아올 때
오렌지 주스 부탁해
will you pick up
some orange juice?
미안한데 난 지금
너무 혼란스러워
Do you mind?
I'm questioning
a lot of things
in my life right now.
네가 오렌지 주스를
좋아하는 것도 혼란스러워?
Is one of those things
your fondness for orange juice?
아니
No.
과육 없는 트로피카나로
Great. Tropicana, no pulp.
Hey, Sheldon.
누구야
Who is it!
쉘든이에요
It's me, Sheldon, Mrs. Wolowitz.
엄마가 아니라
베르나데트야
That's not my mom,
it's Bernadette.
정말?
좀 걱정 된다
Really?
That's very unsettling.
안녕, 쉘든
Hi, Sheldon.
- 안녕
- 무슨 일이야?
- Hi.
- What's up?
친구가 곧 결혼하는데
아직 축하를 안 했지 뭐야
It just occurred to me that I
never formally congratulated you
on your pending nuptials.
악수라도 하려고
버스 타고 왔어
So I hopped on
the first bus and hightailed it
down here to shake your hand.
새신랑 손 좀 잡자
Put 'er there,
you old so-and-so.
연구실에서 볼텐데
Well, I-I'm gonna
see you at work in...
겨우 12시간인데 못 참아?
12 hours-- don't you think it
could have waited until then?
왜 그 생각을 못 했지
Holy smoke,
why didn't I think of that?
하워드, 네가 나보다 낫다
You're a better man
than I, Howard Wolowitz.
악수나 하자
You put 'er there,
you son of a gun!
그러던가
Whatever.
(chuckles)
(buzzing)
My... oh...
it's...
Oh, my God, Howard!
무슨 짓이야?
What did you do?
할로윈 장난이였어
It was a harmless
Halloween prank. Look.
하워드 심장이 약하잖아
Howard has a heart condition!
You know that!
농담인 줄 알았지
Well, I thought
he made that up.
유대인은 모두
심기증 증상을 보이지 않아?
I-Isn't hypochondria a common
idiosyncrasy of Jewish people?
아드레날린이야
This is adrenaline--
we're gonna have
심장에 투입해야 돼
to inject it into his heart.
- 우리가?
- 네가 할 거야
- We are?
- You are. I'm not strong enough
난 힘이 없어서 못 뚫어
to get it through
his chest plate,
기회는 한 번뿐이야
and we've only got one shot.
못하겠어
Oh, no! I can't!
빨리
Hurry!
시간이 없어
We're running out of time!
- 알았어
- 빨리 해
- Okay.
- Just do it!
Oh, God!
하나, 둘
One... two...
셋!
three!
걸려들었네, 바보
Trick or treat, bubbeleh.
뭐?
What?
(laughing)
장난이였어?
No. You mean
this was all a ruse?
내가 왜 이렇게 멍청...
Oh, how could I be so stu...
(buzzing)
(yelling) uuu....
Mmm...
젠장, 못하겠어
Damn it, I can't.
이러면 안돼
I can't do this.
혀 피어싱 때문이야?
Uh, is it my tongue stud?
벌써부터 이러면
'Cause if that
freaks you out,
이따 깜짝 놀랄 거야
you're in for a real
surprise later on.
아니
No, no, no.
못하겠어
I-I can't do this.
정말 하고 싶은데
Believe me,
I really want to.
그런데?
But...?
여자친구가 있어
But I kind of
have a girlfriend.
장난해?
Are you kidding?
그냥 친구해도 되지?
You're cool with you and me
just being friends, right?
어이 없네
(laughs)
I don't believe this.
어떤 부분이?
Wait, I don't...
Which part?
내가 바보 같아서
I'm so stupid.
드디어 좋은 남자
만난 줄 알았는데
I thought for once
I'd met a good guy,
너도 다를 게 없네
but you're just another jackass.
그런 게 아냐
Oh, no, no, you
have it wrong.
나쁜 놈이 되기 전에
멈췄잖아
No. I-I was going
to be a jackass, but
I stopped myself.
아직 좋은 남자야
I stayed
a good guy, so...
섹스는 패스할게
I'm gonna pass on the sex.
넌 충분히 매력적이지만
내가 너무 착해서 그래
But you should
know, that's not
a comment on your hotness
but on my goodness.
그게 내 초능력이야
That's kind of my superpower.
캡틴 굿가이라 할 수 있지
I'm, like, Captain Good Guy.
(exhales)
괜찮아
It's okay.
잘했어
Did the right thing.
이런 멍청이
You idiot!
안녕, 프리야
Hey, Priya.
자기야, 잘 지내?
Hey, sweetheart.
How's it going?
별로야
Uh, not so good.
얘기 좀 하자
We have to talk.
심각해 보이네
Oh, sounds serious.
무슨 일이야?
What's up?
Okay, uh...
시작할게
here it is.
어떤 여자를 만나서
키스까지 했어
I met this girl
and I kissed her,
그리고 지금 너무 괴로워
and I feel
terrible about it.
다시는 그런 일 없을 거야
But it's done, it's never
gonna happen again.
정말 미안해
And I am so, so sorry.
레너드, 진정해
Leonard, relax.
괜찮아
It's okay.
정말?
It is?
그럴 수 있지
Yeah, these things happen.
누구나 다 그래
They happen to everybody.
넌 정말 마음이 넓다
Oh, my God, you are amazing.
네가 아까워
I mean, I don't deserve you.
그런데 누구나 다 그렇다니?
Wh-what do you mean "everybody"?
이런 말 하고 싶지는 않지만
Leonard, I didn't know
if I should tell you,
나도 비슷한 일이 있었어
but I kind of cheated
on you, too.
비슷한?
Kind of?
몇 주 전에
A couple of weeks ago,
전 남자친구랑 잤어
I slept with my ex-boyfriend.
둘 다 실수했네
So, I guess we both messed up
a little.
내가 한 게 실수고
No, no, I messed up a little.
넌 실수 정도가 아니지
You messed up a lot.
크고 작고의 문제가 아니잖아
Well, it's not a competition.
네가 이겼어
Oh... yeah, it is,
and you won.
미안, 다음에 얘기하자
I-I-I'm sorry, I have to go.
이럴 수가
I don't believe this.
(sighs)
(yelling)
버징가!
이제야 제대로 갚았네
Bazinga, punk.
Now we're even.
공대언니 블로그
http://tbbt.tistory.com
== sync, corrected by elderman ==